telecompaper.com 2017-12-22

# Telecompaper Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This policy covers how Telecom.paper BV (“Telecompaper”) treats personal information that Telecompaper collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

### The Information We Collect

This policy applies to all information collected or submitted on Telecompaper website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Company, Name, Address, Telephone Number and E-mail Address.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously unless you have logged in. We do not automatically collect personal information, including your e-mail address. We do use Google Analytics to track utilisation of the www.telecompaper.com website. This information is used only to optimise the site and cannot identify you individually. Please go to cookies below for more information.

Access to certain Telecompaper web pages requires a login and a password. The use of those web pages, and the information from those sites, is be governed by our Terms and Conditions.

At no point does Telecompaper receive any payment details. Adyen provides payment processing services to Telecompaper. Please refer to [www.adyen.com](http://www.adyen.com/) for more information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that many websites write to your computer’s hard drive when you visit them. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of Telecompaper’s website if you do so.

At Telecompaper we use encrypted session cookies that expire at the end of your browsing session. The file is encrypted by our server so it cannot be read by others and is only set when you log in. The encrypted cookies contain: user name, identifier (a unique number in our system), your subscriptions. We also use unencrypted cookies that do not expire (persistent) but these do not identify you. These cookies contain your website preferences for screen-width, website preferences for text size, and the landing page, if these are set by you.

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

To provide you with the latest information about Telecompaper and our products and services, we may occasionally, send you an e-mail newsletter. To stop these e-mails you can unsubscribe via a link in the footer or send an e-mail to [info@telecompaper.com](mailto:info@telecompaper.com) to unsubscribe from our marketing communications.

We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites.

### Data Security

Your Telecompaper account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. Telecompaper safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the internet.

### Third Party Links

Telecompaper’s website contains links to other sites. Telecompaper does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices.

### Updates to this Policy

Telecompaper will amend this privacy statement from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.

### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please e-mail us at [info@telecompaper.com](mailto:info@telecompaper.com).
